bioteck.net 2011-12-22

# BioTecK.net » Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for BioTecK.net**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact me](http://www.bioteck.net/contact/).

At BioTecK.NET, the privacy of the visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy guidelines outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by BioTecK.NET and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
As with almost every website, when you visit BioTecK.NET or any other websites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged. This information includes all kind of information such as; type of browser you use (make sure to use Firefox  ), the server name & IP address through which you access the internet, the date and time you accessed BioTecK.NET, the pages you viewed while visiting the website, and the internet address of the website, if any, from which you linked directly to this website. This information is not personally identifiable!

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**BioTecK.NET may obtain this information by storing a cookie on your computer. With every Internet Browsers like Internet Explorer and  Firefox, you can erase this information from your computer’s hard drive, block all cookies or even receive a warning before a cookie is placed on your system. In order to do so, please click on your browser’s Help Button for more information or use a software which does this for you.

BioTecK.NET uses the non-personally identifiable information primarily to help and improve the website. BioTecK.NET may also use this information to provide information about its website to advertisers, potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on BioTecK.NET.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to BioTecK.NET and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Adgitize, CMF ADS.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on BioTecK.NET send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
BioTecK.NET has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. BioTecK.NET’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

#### About Behrad:

I'm 29 years old, married to a beautiful woman named Jannie, will become a daddy soon and living in Eindhoven, the city of light, The Netherlands.   
From 2006 BioTecK.net is the place where I share my experiences in life, the stuff I do in personal life, show my portfolio and the place where I'll post about my interests; computers & computer related stuff, tips & tricks and basically everything which I want to share.   
Read more [about me](http://www.bioteck.net/about-me/ "About Behrad"), follow me on Twitter [@BioTecK](http://www.twitter.com/BioTecK "Twitter") or [contact me ](http://www.bioteck.net/contact/ "contact me").
